<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Matthew Zegar | Personal Website</title><link>https://mzegar.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Matthew Zegar | Personal Website</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mzegar.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>TTT Reborn</title><link>https://mzegar.github.io/posts/20210608/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mzegar.github.io/posts/20210608/</guid><description>Trying to figure out why this is broken&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>s&amp;box</title><link>https://mzegar.github.io/posts/sandbox/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mzegar.github.io/posts/sandbox/</guid><description>I was recently given access to s&amp;amp;box (thanks to Minh &amp;amp; Garry). The amount of potential in terms of creating amazing gamemodes is magnitudes higher than anything found in Garry&amp;rsquo;s Mod.
First &amp;ldquo;Addon&amp;rdquo; Already within hours of receiving s&amp;amp;box I have published my first addon. It allows users to easily create a crosshair similar to what is found in most popular FPS games.
https://github.com/mzegar/sbox-crosshair
What&amp;rsquo;s next The end goal is remaking the popular Half-Life mod &amp;ldquo;The Specialists&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Hugo, Another Static Site Generator</title><link>https://mzegar.github.io/posts/static-site-generators/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mzegar.github.io/posts/static-site-generators/</guid><description>I always took pride in creating my personal websites basically from scratch. But, what&amp;rsquo;s the point of jumping through hoops when other developers already have for me. At this current time, static site generators are the new hip thing, so let&amp;rsquo;s try one out.
Hugo is a static site generator that basically wraps a bunch of markdown files. This got me excited as previously updating my website was a pain. I had to go through this typical process&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>https://mzegar.github.io/projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mzegar.github.io/projects/</guid><description>S&amp;amp;box Crosshair C#, SCSS, s&amp;amp;box (May 2021)
A complete static crosshair system built for usage within s&amp;amp;box Retter - Flutter Reddit App Dart, Flutter (Jun 2020)
A complete Reddit experience built using Flutter Open sourced and contributed to by other developers Built for iOS and Android Social Gaming App C++, GoogleTest, CMake (Jan 2020 - Apr 2020)
Developed the application using modern C++ practices Created a build system using CMake Wrote extensive testing for the application using the GoogleTest framework Led an eight-person group as the &amp;ldquo;Project Manager&amp;rdquo; Database Interface Java, JavaFX, Spring (Apr 2019)</description></item></channel></rss>